Guide to the Lincoln Steffens Papers
Rare Book and Manuscript Library Columbia University Libraries
- Series III. Letters of Lincoln Steffens
  - Steffens, Lincoln
    - To Joseph Steffens, 1896 October 15, (a.l.s., 2p.) (Box 64)
    - To Joseph Steffens, 1896 November 6, (t.l., 2p.) (Box 64)
    - To Joseph Steffens, 1896 November 9, (a.l.s., 5p.) (Box 64)
    - To Joseph Steffens, 1897 January 7, (a.l.s., 2p.) (Box 64)
    - To Joseph Steffens, 1897 July 6, (a.l.s., 1p., with envelope) (Box 64)
    - To Joseph Steffens, 1897 October 13, (t.l.s., 2p.) (Box 64)
    - To Joseph Steffens, 1897 November 7, (a.l.s., 2p.) (Box 64)
    - To Joseph Steffens, 1897 November 8, (a.l.s., 1p.) (Box 64)
    - To Joseph Steffens, 1898 March 23, (t.l.s., 2p.) (Box 64)
    - To Joseph Steffens, 1898 April 8, (t.l.s., 2p., with envelope) (Box 64)
    - To Joseph Steffens, circa 1898 May, (a.l.s., 2p., with envelope) (Box 64)
    - To Joseph Steffens, 1898 May 2, (a.l.s., 1p.) (Box 64)
    - To Joseph Steffens, 1898 May 16, (a.l.s., 1p.) (Box 64)
    - To Joseph Steffens, 1898 August 2, (a.l.s., 2p.) (Box 64)
    - To Joseph Steffens, 1898 August 9, (a.l.s., 2p.) (Box 64)
    - To Joseph Steffens, 1898 October 7, (a.l.s., 2p.) (Box 64)
    - To Joseph Steffens, 1898 October 21, (a.l.s., 2p.) (Box 64)
    - To Joseph Steffens, 1898 November 15, (a.l.s., 2p.) (Box 64)
    - To Joseph Steffens, 1898 December 10, (t.l.s., 2p., with envelope) (Box 64)
    - To Joseph Steffens, 1899 January 4, (a.l.s., 2p.) (Box 64)
    - To Joseph Steffens, 1899 March 8, (a.l.s., 2p.) (Box 64)
    - To Joseph Steffens, 1899 June 30, (a.l.s., 2p., with envelope) (Box 64)
    - To Joseph Steffens, 1899 August 13, (a.l.s., 2p.) (Box 64)
    - To Joseph Steffens, 1900 January 13, (a.l.s., 2p.) (Box 64)
    - To Joseph Steffens, 1900 February, (a.l.s., 1p.) (Box 64)
    - To Elizabeth Louise Symes Steffens, 1900 May 20, (t.l.s., 2p.) (Box 64)
    - To Joseph Steffens, 1900 June 6, (a.l.s., 2p.) (Box 64)
    - To Joseph Steffens, 1900 July 30, (a.l.s., 2p., with envelope) (Box 64)
    - To Joseph Steffens, 1900 September 11, (a.l.s., 1p., with envelope) (Box 64)
    - To Joseph Steffens, 1900 November 11, (a.l.s., 2p.) (Box 64)
    - To Joseph Steffens, 1900 December 5, (a.l.s., 2p.) (Box 64)
    - To Joseph Steffens, 1900 December 7, (a.l.s., 4p.) (Box 64)
    - To Joseph Steffens, 1901 March 11, (a.l.s., 1p.) (Box 65)
    - To Joseph Steffens, 1901 May 4, (a.l.s., 2p., with envelope) (Box 65)
    - To Joseph Steffens, 1901 May 7, (a.l.s., 2p.) (Box 65)
    - To Joseph Steffens, 1901 May 24, (a.l.s., 1p.) (Box 65)
    - To Joseph Steffens, 1901 May 25, (a.l.s., 2p., with envelope) (Box 65)
    - To Joseph Steffens, 1901 June 20, (a.l.s., 4p., with envelope) (Box 65)
    - To Elizabeth Louise Symes Steffens, 1901 July 11-12, (a.l.s., 4p.) (Box 65)
    - To William Neely, 1901 July 14, (a.l.s., 4p.) (Box 65)
    - To Joseph Steffens, 1901 August 27, (a.l.s., 2p.) (Box 65)
    - To Joseph Steffens, 1901 September 4, (a.l.s., 4p., with envelope) (Box 65)
    - To Joseph Steffens, 1901 September 14, (a.l.s., 2p.) (Box 65)
    - To Joseph Steffens, 1901 September 23, (a.l.s., 1p.) (Box 65)
    - To Joseph Steffens, 1901 September 28, (a.l.s., 2p.) (Box 65)
    - To Joseph Steffens, 1901 November 2, (a.l.s., 2p.) (Box 65)
    - To Joseph Steffens, 1901 December 29, (a.l.s., 2p., with envelope) (Box 65)
    - To Joseph Steffens, 1902 January 16, (a.l.s., 2p.) (Box 65)
    - To Joseph Steffens, 1902 April 11, (a.l.s., 2p.) (Box 65)
    - To Joseph Steffens, 1902 May 18, (a.l.s., 2p.) (Box 65)
    - To Joseph Steffens, 1902 August 5, (t.l.s., 2p., with envelope) (Box 65)
    - To Joseph Steffens, 1902 August 15, (t.l.s., 2p., with envelope) (Box 65)
    - To Joseph Steffens, 1903 September 21, (a.l.s., 3p.) (Box 65)
    - To Joseph Steffens, 1903 October 17, (a.l.s., 4p.) (Box 65)
    - To Joseph Steffens, 1903 October 26, (a.l.s., 2p.) (Box 65)
    - To Joseph Steffens, 1903 December, (a.l.s., 3p.) (Box 65)
    - To Joseph Steffens, 1903 December 1, (a.l.s., 2p.) (Box 65)
    - To Joseph Steffens, 1903 December 13, (a.l.s., 3p.) (Box 65)
    - To Elizabeth Louise Symes Steffens, 1903 December 15, (a.l.s., 2p.) (Box 65)
    - To Joseph Steffens, 1904 January 26, (a.l.s., 2p.) (Box 65)
    - To Joseph Steffens, 1904 February 7, (a.l.s., 2p.) (Box 65)
    - To Joseph Steffens, 1904 February 14, (a.l.s., 3p.) (Box 65)
    - To Joseph Steffens, 1904 March 5, (a.l.s., 2p.) (Box 65)
    - To Joseph Steffens, 1904 April 4, (a.l.s.) (Box 65)
    - To Joseph Steffens, 1904 April 10, (a.l.s., 2p.) (Box 65)
    - To Joseph Steffens, 1904 April 20, (a.l.s., 2p.) (Box 65)
    - To Joseph Steffens, 1904 April 26, (a.l.s., 2p.) (Box 65)
    - To Joseph Steffens, 1904 August 28, (a.l.s., 1p.) (Box 65)
    - To Joseph Steffens, 1904 October 2, (a.l.s., 2p.) (Box 65)
    - To Joseph Steffens, 1904 October 20, (a.l.s., 2p.) (Box 65)
    - To Joseph Steffens, circa 1904 November 27, (a.l.s., 2p., with envelope) (Box 65)
    - To Joseph Steffens, 1905 February 13, (a.l.s., 2p.) (Box 65)
    - To Joseph Steffens, 1905 August 5, (a.l.s., 3p.) (Box 65)
    - To Joseph Steffens, 1905 November 5, (a.l.s., 2p.) (Box 65)
    - To Joseph Steffens, 1906 March 26, (a.l.s., 2p., written on letter from Dietrich H. Steffens to Lincoln Steffens) (Box 65)
    - To Joseph Steffens, 1906 June 3, (a.l.s., 3p.) (Box 65)
    - To Joseph Steffens, 1906 June 21, (a.l.s., 2p.) (Box 65)
    - To Joseph Steffens, 1907 August 16, (a.l.s., 2p.) (Box 65)
    - To Joseph Steffens, 1907 August 27, (a.l.s., 4p.) (Box 65)
    - To Joseph Steffens, 1907 October 20, (a.l.s., 1p.) (Box 65)
    - To George E. Chamberlain, 1908, (a.l., draft, 4p.) (Box 65)
    - To [G.H.] McMahan, 1980, (a.l.s., draft, 4p.) (Box 65)
    - To J.D. Porter, 1908, (a.l., draft, 6p.) (Box 65)
    - To [Hamnet P.] Hill, 1908 February 15, (a.l.s., 2p.) (Box 65)
    - To Joseph Steffens, 1908 February 28, (a.l.s., 2p.) (Box 65)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1908 February 28, (a.l.s.) (Box 65)
    - To Elizabeth Louise Symes Steffens, 1908 October 3, (a.l.s., 2p.) (Box 65)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1908 November 1, (a.l.s., 2p.) (Box 65)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1908 November 9, (a.l.s., 2p.) (Box 65)
    - To Elizabeth Louise Symes Steffens, 1908 December 6, (a.l.s., 2p.) (Box 65)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1908 December 13, (a.l.s., 2p.) (Box 65)
    - To Lou Steffens Suggett (1st Mrs. Allen H.), 1909 February, (a.l.s., 2p.) (Box 65)
    - To Joseph Steffens, 1909 February 14, (a.l.s., 3p.) (Box 65)
    - To Allen H. Suggett, 1909 March 13, (a.l.s., 2p.) (Box 65)
    - To Joseph Steffens, 1909 April 28, (a.l.s., 2p.) (Box 65)
    - To Joseph Steffens, 1909 May 15, (a.l.s., 2p.) (Box 65)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1909 May 31, (a.l.s., 4p.) (Box 65)
    - To Joseph Steffens, 1909 August 7, (a.l.s., 3p.) (Box 65)
    - To Lou Steffens Suggett (1st Mrs. Allen H.), 1909 August 24, (t.l.s., 2p.) (Box 65)
    - To Joseph Steffens, 1909 September 14, (t.l.s., 2p., with envelope) (Box 65)
    - To Joseph Steffens, 1909 September 23, (t.l.s., 2p., with envelope) (Box 65)
    - To Lou Steffens Suggett (1st Mrs. Allen H.), 1909 September 29, (a.l.s., 2p.) (Box 65)
    - To Joseph Steffens, 1909 November 13, (t.l.s., 1p., with envelope) (Box 65)
    - To Elizabeth Louise Symes Steffens, 1909 December 21, (t.l.s., 2p., with envelope) (Box 65)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1910 January 4, (a.l.s., 2p.) (Box 65)
    - To Elizabeth Louise Symes Steffens, 1910 February 7, (a.l.s., 2p.) (Box 65)
    - To Joseph Steffens, 1910 March 8, (t.l.s., 2p., with envelope) (Box 65)
    - To Elizabeth Louise Symes Steffens, 1910 March 25, (t.l.s., 2p.) (Box 65)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1910 April 9, (t.l.s., 2p., with envelope) (Box 65)
    - To Joseph Steffens, 1910 May 24, (t.l.s., 3p., with envelope) (Box 65)
    - To Dot Steffens Hollister (Mrs. John James) and John James Hollister, circa 1910 June 13, (a.l.s., 4p.) (Box 65)
    - To Allen H. Suggett, 1910 June 30, (t.l.s., 3p.) (Box 65)
    - To Dot Steffens Hollister (Mrs. John James), 1910 July 1, (t.l.s., 2p.) (Box 65)
    - To Lou Steffens Suggett (1st Mrs. Allen H.) and Allen H. Suggett, 1910 August 26, (a.l.s., 2p.) (Box 65)
    - To Allen H. Suggett, 1910 August 29, (t.l.s., 2p.) (Box 65)
    - To Joseph Steffens, 1910 August 29, (t.l.s., 2p.) (Box 65)
    - To Allen H. Suggett, 1910 August 30, (a.l.s., 2p.) (Box 65)
    - To Lou Steffens Suggett (1st Mrs. Allen H.), 1910 September 8, (a.l.s., 2p.) (Box 65)
    - To Dot Steffens Hollister (Mrs. John James), 1910 September 13, (a.l.s., 2p.) (Box 65)
    - To Allen H. Suggett, 1910 September 16, (t.l.s., 2p.) (Box 65)
    - To Allen H. Suggett, 1910 October 2, (t.l.s., 2p.) (Box 65)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1910 October 13, (a.l.s., 2p.) (Box 65)
    - To Allen H. Suggett, 1910 October 18, (a.l.s., 3p.) (Box 65)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1910 October 18, (a.l.s., 2p.) (Box 65)
    - To Allen H. Suggett, 1910 October 22, (a.l.s., 3p.) (Box 65)
    - To Joseph Steffens, 1910 October 22, (a.l.s., 2p.) (Box 65)
    - To Lou Steffens Suggett (1st Mrs. Allen H.) and Allen H. Suggett, 1910 October 30, (a.l.s., 2p.) (Box 65)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1910 November 9, (a.l.s., 1p.) (Box 65)
    - To Allen H. Suggett, 1910 November 10, (a.l.s., 2p.) (Box 65)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1910 November 13, (a.l.s., 2p.) (Box 65)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1910 November 14, (a.l.s., 1p.) (Box 65)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1910 November 29, (t.l.s., 2p.) (Box 65)
    - To Allen H. Suggett, 1910 December 13, (t.l.s., 2p.) (Box 65)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1910 December 25, (a.l.s., 4p.) (Box 65)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1910 December 28, (a.l.s., 2p.) (Box 65)
    - To Joseph Steffens, 1911 January 5, (a.l.s., 3p.) (Box 65)
    - To Dot Steffens Hollister (Mrs. John James), 1911 January 5, (a.l.s., 4p.) (Box 65)
    - To Lou Steffens Suggett (1st Mrs. Allen H.) and Allen H. Suggett, 1911 January 11, (a.l.s., 2p.) (Box 65)
    - To Dot Steffens Hollister (Mrs. John James), 1911 January 20, (a.l.s., 3p.) (Box 65)
    - To Allen H. Suggett, 1911 January 21, (a.l.s., 3p.) (Box 65)
    - To Lou Steffens Suggett (1st Mrs. Allen H.), 1911 January 22, (a.l.s., 2p.) (Box 65)
    - To Lou Steffens Suggett (1st Mrs. Allen H.) and Allen H. Suggett, 1911 January 30, (a.l.s., 3p.) (Box 65)
    - To Allen H. Suggett, 1911 February 7, (a.l.s., 3p.) (Box 65)
    - To Allen H. Suggett, 1911 February 11, (a.l.s., 3p.) (Box 65)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1911 February 14, (a.l.s., 4p., with envelope) (Box 65)
    - To Dot Steffens Hollister (Mrs. John James), 1911 February 24, (t.l.s., 3p., with autograph postscript) (Box 65)
    - To Allen H. Suggett, 1911 February 28, (a.l.s., 2p.) (Box 65)
    - To Marie Jenney Howe, 1911 March 5, (a.l.s., 2p., with envelope) (Box 65)
    - To Allen H. Suggett, 1911 March 6, (a.l.s., 3p., with autograph postsecript) (Box 65)
    - To Dot Steffens Hollister (Mrs. John James), 1911 March 20, (a.l.s., 4p.) (Box 65)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1911 June 4, (a.l.s., 3p.) (Box 65)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1911 June 5, (t.l., 2p., signed by proxy) (Box 65)
    - To Marie Jenney Howe, 1911 June 8, (a.l.s., 3p., with envelope) (Box 65)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1911 June 15, (a.l.s., 2p.) (Box 65)
    - To Lou Steffens Suggett (1st Mrs. Allen H.) and Allen H. Suggett, 1911 June 15, (a.l.s., 2p.) (Box 65)
    - To Lou Steffens Suggett (1st Mrs. Allen H.) and Allen H. Suggett, 1911 July 3, (a.l.s., 4p.) (Box 65)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1911 July 14, (a.l.s., 4p.) (Box 65)
    - To Joseph Steffens, 1911 August 22, (a.l.s., 2p.) (Box 65)
    - To Joseph Steffens, 1911 September 11, (a.l.s., 2p.) (Box 65)
    - To Allen H. Suggett and Lou Steffens Suggett (1st Mrs. Allen H.), 1911 September 23, (a.l.s., 4p., with envelope) (Box 65)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1911 October 29, (a.l.s.) (Box 65)
    - To Dot Steffens Hollister (Mrs. John James), 1911 November, (a.l.s., 4p.) (Box 65)
    - To Lou Steffens Suggett (1st Mrs. Allen H.), 1911 November, (a.l.s., 2p.) (Box 65)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1911 November, (a.l.s., 2p.) (Box 65)
    - To Joseph Steffens, 1911 November 3, (a.l.s., 3p.) (Box 65)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1911 November 17, (a.l.s., 3p., with envelope) (Box 65)
    - To Dot Steffens Hollister (Mrs. John James), 1911 November 20, (a.l.s., 1p.) (Box 65)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), circa 1911 November 29, (a.l.s., 2p., with envelope) (Box 65)
    - To ASH, circa 1911 December 4, (a.l.s., 2p., with envelope) (Box 65)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), circa 1911 December 11, (a.l.s., 3p., with envelope) (Box 65)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1911 December 18?, (a.l.s., 3p.) (Box 65)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1911 December 24, (a.l.s., 4p.) (Box 65)
    - To Allen H. Suggett and Lou Steffens Suggett (1st Mrs. Allen H.), 1911 December 24, (a.l.s., 4p.) (Box 65)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1912 January 11, (a.l.s., 4p.) (Box 66)
    - To Lou Steffens Suggett (1st Mrs. Allen H.), 1912 January 17, (a.l.s., 3p.) (Box 66)
    - To Allen H. Suggett, 1912 January 24, (a.l.s., 3p.) (Box 66)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1912 January 28, (a.l.s., 4p.) (Box 66)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1912 February 1, (a.l.s., 3p.) (Box 66)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1912 February 7, (a.l.s., 3p.) (Box 66)
    - To Allen H. Suggett, 1912 February 8, (t.l.s., 1p., damaged) (Box 66)
    - To Dot Steffens Hollister (Mrs. John James), 1912 February 21, (t.l.s.) (Box 66)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1912 February 27, (t.l.s., with envelope) (Box 66)
    - To John James Hollister, 1912 February 27, (a.l.s., 3p.) (Box 66)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1912 February 28, (a.l.s., 3p.) (Box 66)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1912 March 2, (a.l.s., 4p.) (Box 66)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1912 March 5, (a.l.s., 2p.) (Box 66)
    - To Lou Steffens Suggett (1st Mrs. Allen H.) and Allen H. Suggett, 1912 March 7, (a.l.s., 3p.) (Box 66)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1912 March 12, (a.l.s., 6p.) (Box 66)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1912 March 30, (t.l.s., 2p., with envelope) (Box 66)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1912 April 11, (a.l.s., 4p.) (Box 66)
    - To Allen H. Suggett and Lou Steffens Suggett (1st Mrs. Allen H.), 1912 April 18, (a.l.s., 3p.) (Box 66)
    - To Dot Steffens Hollister (Mrs. John James) and John James Hollister, circa 1912 May, (a.l.s., 2p.) (Box 66)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1912 May 1, (a.l.s.) (Box 66)
    - To Lou Steffens Suggett (1st Mrs. Allen H.) and Allen H. Suggett, 1912 May 1, (a.l.s.) (Box 66)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), Lou Steffens Suggett (1st Mrs. Allen H.), and Allen H. Suggett, 1912 May 3, (a.l.s.) (Box 66)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1912 May 8, (a.l.s., 2p.) (Box 66)
    - To Allen H. Suggett, 1912 May 8, (a.l.s., 3p., with envelope) (Box 66)
    - To Dot Steffens Hollister (Mrs. John James), 1912 May 17, (a.l.s., 2p.) (Box 66)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), circa 1912 May 17, (a.l.s., 3p., with envelope) (Box 66)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1912 May 24, (a.l.s., 2p.) (Box 66)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1912 May 31, (a.l.s., 4p., with envelope) (Box 66)
    - To Dot Steffens Hollister (Mrs. John James), 1912 June 14, (a.l.s.) (Box 66)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1912 June 17?, (a.l.s., 4p.) (Box 66)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1912 June 3, (a.l.s., 3p.) (Box 66)
    - To Lou Steffens Suggett (1st Mrs. Allen H.) and Allen H. Suggett, 1912 June 3, (a.l.s., 2p.) (Box 66)
    - To Lou Steffens Suggett (1st Mrs. Allen H.) and Allen H. Suggett, 1912 June 5, (a.l.s., 2p.) (Box 66)
    - To Dot Steffens Hollister (Mrs. John James) and John James Hollister, 1912 June 5?, (a.l.s., 3p.) (Box 66)
    - To Lou Steffens Suggett (1st Mrs. Allen H.), 1912 June 6, (a.l.s., 2p.) (Box 66)
    - To John James Hollister, 1912 June 6, (a.l.s., 2p.) (Box 66)
    - To Dot Steffens Hollister (Mrs. John James), 1912 June 10, (a.l.s., 4p.) (Box 66)
    - To Dot Steffens Hollister (Mrs. John James), 1912 June 12, (a.l.s., 3p.) (Box 66)
    - To Allen H. Suggett, 1912 June 13, (a.l.s., 2p.) (Box 66)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1912 June 19, (a.l.s., 4p., with envelope) (Box 66)
    - To Lou Steffens Suggett (1st Mrs. Allen H.) and Allen H. Suggett, 1912 June 19, (a.l.s., 4p.) (Box 66)
    - To Dot Steffens Hollister (Mrs. John James), 1912 June 19, (a.l.s., 4p.) (Box 66)
    - To Dot Steffens Hollister (Mrs. John James) and John James Hollister, 1912 June 21, (a.l.s., 4p.) (Box 66)
    - To Lou Steffens Suggett (1st Mrs. Allen H.), 1912 June 22, (a.l.s., 4p.) (Box 66)
    - To Lou Steffens Suggett (1st Mrs. Allen H.), 1912 June 22, (a.l.s., 2p.) (Box 66)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1912 June 25, (a.l.s., 6p.) (Box 66)
    - To Dot Steffens Hollister (Mrs. John James), 1912 June 26, (a.l.s., 4p.) (Box 66)
    - To Dot Steffens Hollister (Mrs. John James), 1912 July 9, (a.l.s., 2p.) (Box 66)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1912 July 8, (a.l.s., 2p.) (Box 66)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1912 July 12, (a.l.s., 3p.) (Box 66)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1912 July 20, (a.l.s., 3p.) (Box 66)
    - To Dot Steffens Hollister (Mrs. John James) and John James Hollister, 1912 July 21, (a.l.s., 2p.) (Box 66)
    - To Allen H. Suggett, 1912 July 22, (a.l.s., 3p.) (Box 66)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), circa 1912 July 29, (a.l.s., 2p., with envelope) (Box 66)
    - To Allen H. Suggett, 1912 July 31, (a.l.s., 3p.) (Box 66)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1912 August, (a.l.s., 2p.) (Box 66)
    - To Dietrich H. Steffens, 1912 August 13, (a.l., 2p.) (Box 66)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1912 August 13, (a.l.s., 2p., with envelope) (Box 66)
    - To Clinton Hollister, 1912 August 13, (a.l.s., 4p.) (Box 66)
    - To Jane Hollister, 1912 August 14, (a.l.s., 2p.) (Box 66)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1912 August 22, (a.l.s., 3p.) (Box 66)
    - To Allen H. Suggett, 1912 September 12, (a.l.s., 4p.) (Box 66)
    - To Miriam W. Johnson, 1912 September 27, (t.l., 1p.) (Box 66)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1912 October 3, (a.l.s., 3p.) (Box 66)
    - To Dot Steffens Hollister (Mrs. John James) and John James Hollister, 1912 October 3, (a.l.s., 3p.) (Box 66)
    - To Lou Steffens Suggett (1st Mrs. Allen H.), 1912 October 8, (a.l.s., 4p.) (Box 66)
    - To Dot Steffens Hollister (Mrs. John James), 1912 October 17, (a.l.s., 5p.) (Box 66)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1912 October 22, (a.l.s., 3p.) (Box 66)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1912 October 22, (a.l.s., 4p.) (Box 66)
    - To Dot Steffens Hollister (Mrs. John James), 1912 October 24, (a.l.s., 4p.) (Box 66)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1912 November 14, (a.l.s., 3p.) (Box 66)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1912 November 14, (a.l.s., 4p.) (Box 66)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), circa 1912 November 19, (a.l.s., 4p.) (Box 66)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1912 November 19, (a.l.s., 4p.) (Box 66)
    - To Lou Steffens Suggett (1st Mrs. Allen H.) and Allen H. Suggett, 1912 November 19, (a.l.s., 4p.) (Box 66)
    - To Dot Steffens Hollister (Mrs. John James), 1912 November 22, (a.l.s., 4p.) (Box 66)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1912 November 24, (a.l.s., 4p.) (Box 66)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1912 November 26, (a.l.s., 2p.) (Box 66)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1912 December 9, (a.l.s., 3p.) (Box 66)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1912 December 11, (a.l.s., 3p.) (Box 66)
    - To Allen H. Suggett, 1912 December 20, (a.l.s., 4p.) (Box 66)
    - To Lou Steffens Suggett (1st Mrs. Allen H.), 1912 December 23, (a.l.s., 2p.) (Box 66)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1912 December 23, (a.l.s., 3p.) (Box 66)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1913 January 2, (a.l.s., 2p.) (Box 66)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1913 January 3, (a.l.s., 3p.) (Box 66)
    - To Clinton and Jane Hollister, 1913 January 9, (a.l.s., 4p.) (Box 66)
    - To Dot Steffens Hollister (Mrs. John James), 1913 January 11, (a.l.s., 3p.) (Box 66)
    - To Dot Steffens Hollister (Mrs. John James), 1913 January 16, (a.l.s.) (Box 66)
    - To Lou Steffens Suggett (1st Mrs. Allen H.) and Allen H. Suggett, 1913 January 19, (a.l.s.) (Box 66)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1913 January 22, (a.l.s., 3p.) (Box 66)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1913 January 24, (a.l.s., 3p., with envelope) (Box 66)
  - Suggett, Lou Steffens-- To Jane Hollister, 1913 January 28, (a.l.s., 2p.) (Box 66)
  - Steffens, Lincoln
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1913 February 4, (a.l.s., 3p., with envelope) (Box 66)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1913 February 11, (a.l.s., 2p.) (Box 66)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1913 February 13, (a.l.s., 2p., with envelope) (Box 66)
    - To Lou Steffens Suggett (1st Mrs. Allen H.) and Allen H. Suggett, 1913 February 13, (a.l.s., 2p.) (Box 66)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1913 February 18, (a.l.s., 2p., with envelope) (Box 66)
    - To Lou Steffens Suggett (1st Mrs. Allen H.) and Allen H. Suggett, 1913 February 18, (a.l.s., 1p.) (Box 66)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1913 February 23, (a.l.s., 2p., with envelope) (Box 66)
    - To Dot Steffens Hollister (Mrs. John James), circa 1913 February 25, (a.l.s., 2p.) (Box 66)
    - To Clinton Hollister, 1913 February 25, (a.l.s., 2p.) (Box 66)
    - To Jane Hollister, 1913 February 25, (a.l.s., 2p.) (Box 66)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1913 February 28, (a.l.s., 2p., with envelope) (Box 66)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), circa 1913 March 5, (a.l.s., 2p.) (Box 66)
    - To Lou Steffens Suggett (1st Mrs. Allen H.), 1913 March 5, (a.l.s., 2p.) (Box 66)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1913 March 27, (a.l.s., 2p.) (Box 66)
    - To Dot Steffens Hollister (Mrs. John James), 1913 March 27, (a.l.s., 2p.) (Box 66)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1913 April 19, (a.l.s., with envelope) (Box 66)
    - To Lou Steffens Suggett (1st Mrs. Allen H.), circa 1913 June, (a.l.s., 4p., with envelope) (Box 66)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1913 June 6, (a.l.s., 3p.) (Box 66)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1913 June 29, (a.l.s., 3p.) (Box 66)